(Adapted from the novel "Counterattack" by Chai Ji Dan)
(مقتبس من رواية "هجوم مضاد" للكاتب تشاي جي دان)
(Episode 11, Come on, Let's Go Home and Get Registered)
(الحلقة 11، هيا بنا نعود إلى المنزل ونسجل)
Dr. Jiang, how many boxes of aspirin do we need?
دكتور جيانج، كم علبة أسبرين نحتاج؟
Three.
ثلاثة.
Three boxes.
ثلاثة صناديق.
There are only three days left...
لم يتبق سوى ثلاثة أيام...
until the ultimatum Chi Cheng gave me.
حتى الإنذار الذي أعطاني إياه تشي تشنغ.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Dr. Jiang.
الدكتور جيانج.
It's been a while, Dr. Jiang.
لقد مر وقت طويل، دكتور جيانج.
Aren't you going to pursue someone else?
ألا تنوي ملاحقة شخص آخر؟
Why did you still come here?
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا مرة أخرى؟
If I'm pursuing someone else,
إذا كنت أسعى وراء شخص آخر،
shouldn't you feel glad?
ألا يجب عليك أن تشعر بالسعادة؟
I am.
أنا أكون.
Don't I look happy?
هل أبدو سعيدا؟
Don't I?
ألا أفعل ذلك؟
Dr. Jiang.
الدكتور جيانج.
How can someone like you...
كيف يمكن لشخص مثلك...
be someone's teacher?
أن تكون معلما لشخص ما؟
Doctor.
طبيب.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
She said she doesn't want to live anymore.
قالت أنها لا تريد أن تعيش بعد الآن.
Treat her.
تعاملها.
- Where are you going? - Chubby!
- إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟ - ممتلئ الجسم!
- Get the first-aid kit. - Okay.
- احصل على مجموعة الإسعافات الأولية. - حسنًا.
- Cheng Yu, come and help me.
- تشنغ يو، تعال وساعدني.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Hurry.
عجل.
You can both go first.
يمكنكم الذهاب كلاكما أولاً.
I'll stay here.
سأبقى هنا.
Okay. I'll get going then.
حسنًا، سأذهب إذن.
Bye.
الوداع.
If her root problem isn't solved,
إذا لم يتم حل مشكلتها الجذرية،
it's useless for you to stay here either.
ليس من المفيد لك البقاء هنا أيضًا.
If I don't watch over her, it's the same as not saving her.
إذا لم أراقبها، فهذا مثل عدم إنقاذها.
You should go home first.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب إلى المنزل أولاً.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
(The message was sent, but was rejected by the other party)
(تم إرسال الرسالة ولكن تم رفضها من قبل الطرف الآخر)
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Why did he do that to me?
لماذا فعل بي ذلك؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Calm down first.
اهدأ أولاً.
Here. Let me see.
هنا. دعني أرى.
- Let go! - What are you doing?
-اتركه! -ماذا تفعل؟
Let go.
اتركه.
Give it to me.
أعطيني إياه.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Xiao Shuai, are you all right?
شياو شواي، هل أنت بخير؟
Xiao Shuai.
شياو شواي.
- What exactly do you want? - Cheng Yu, don't act this way.
- ماذا تريد بالضبط؟ - تشنغ يو، لا تتصرف بهذه الطريقة.
Let her die.
دعها تموت.
She's doing this over a guy. Does she deserve to live?
إنها تفعل هذا من أجل رجل. هل تستحق الحياة؟
Because of playboys like you,
بسبب المستهترين مثلك،
those who take relationships seriously...
أولئك الذين يأخذون العلاقات على محمل الجد...
lose the courage to love themselves.
يفقدون الشجاعة لمحبة أنفسهم.
Xiao Shuai.
شياو شواي.
I was speaking up for you.
لقد كنت أتحدث نيابة عنك.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Calm down.
اهدأ.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
- I didn't do it on purpose. - It's okay.
- لم أفعل ذلك عمدًا. - لا بأس.
I know it was an accident.
أعلم أنها كانت حادثة.
Lie down and rest.
استلقي واستريح.
Don't think too much first.
لا تفكر كثيرا أولا.
It's all right.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
Get some rest.
احصل على بعض الراحة.
Xiao Shuai.
شياو شواي.
Let me treat your wound first.
دعني أعالج جرحك أولاً.
I'm a doctor.
انا طبيب.
I can do it myself.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
It's inconvenient for you to do it yourself.
من غير الملائم لك أن تفعل ذلك بنفسك.
Let me do it.
دعني افعل ذلك.
Come on. Be careful.
هيا، كن حذرا.
Slowly.
ببطء.
It might hurt a little.
ربما يؤلم قليلاً.
Bear with it a bit.
تحمل الأمر قليلا.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
I'll be gentle then.
سوف أكون لطيفا إذن.
Earlier,
سابقًا،
didn't you leave?
ألم تغادر؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
I ran some errands,
لقد قمت ببعض المهمات،
then I came back.
ثم عدت.
It's late.
إنه متأخر.
What errands could you have?
ما هي المهمات التي يمكن أن تكون لديك؟
Didn't Wu Suo Wei tell me...
ألم يخبرني وو سو وي...
to pursue someone else?
لملاحقة شخص آخر؟
I went out to see...
خرجت لرؤية...
if there's anyone suitable.
إذا كان هناك أي شخص مناسب.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I'll do it myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Okay.
تمام.
So...
لذا...
you don't like that idea.
أنت لا تحب هذه الفكرة.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I'll think of another one for you.
سأفكر في واحد آخر لك.
Endure it a bit.
تحملها قليلا.
Dr. Jiang, I'm going home.
الدكتور جيانج، سأعود إلى المنزل.
Thank you so much for taking care of me.
شكرا جزيلا لك على رعايتك لي.
Xiao Zhuang.
شياو تشوانغ.
You must love yourself more.
يجب عليك أن تحب نفسك أكثر.
Call me if you need anything.
اتصل بي إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء.
(Xiao Zhuang)
(شياو تشوانغ)
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Get to the point.
انتقل إلى النقطة الأساسية.
I've come up...
لقد صعدت...
with a perfect, new plan.
مع خطة جديدة مثالية.
Do you want to hear it?
هل تريد سماعها؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
- Hello? - Da Wei.
- مرحبًا؟ - دا وي.
I have good news for you.
عندي لك أخبار جيدة.
It will definitely make you happy.
إنه سيجعلك سعيدا بالتأكيد.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Chi Cheng's Snake Lord...
سيد الثعابين تشي تشنغ...
is coming back to the country in three days.
سيعود إلى البلاد خلال ثلاثة أيام.
His flight lands at midnight.
تهبط طائرته في منتصف الليل.
After that, we'll be free.
بعد ذلك سنكون أحرارًا.
Snake Lord?
سيد الثعابين؟
What Snake Lord?
ما هو سيد الثعابين؟
Which Snake Lord do you think I'm talking about?
من هو سيد الثعابين الذي تعتقد أنني أتحدث عنه؟
The one Chi Cheng has been missing for six years.
لقد كان تشي تشنغ مفقودًا لمدة ست سنوات.
And for his sake,
ومن أجله،
he was willing to turn against Guo Cheng Yu.
وكان على استعداد للانقلاب ضد قوه تشنغ يو.
The handsome Mr. Wang.
السيد وانغ الوسيم.
So what if he's coming back?
فماذا لو عاد؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
If his original lover is back, he'll have no time for us.
إذا عاد حبيبه الأصلي، فلن يكون لديه وقت لنا.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
Chi Cheng will lose interest in you...
تشي تشنغ سوف يفقد الاهتمام بك...
and won't bother me too.
ولن يزعجني أيضًا.
Guo Cheng Yu had a thing with him before.
لقد كان لدى قوه تشنغ يو شيئًا معه من قبل.
Maybe after he seduces Guo Cheng Yu,
ربما بعد أن أغوى قوه تشنغ يو،
I'll be completely free.
سوف أكون حرا تماما.
It's killing three birds with one stone.
إنه قتل ثلاثة عصافير بحجر واحد.
When else can you get something as great as this?
متى يمكنك الحصول على شيء عظيم مثل هذا؟
It's not bad.
إنه ليس سيئا.
Da Wei, tell me. Aren't we lucky?
دا وي، أخبرني. أليس محظوظًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
I have a patient here. I'll get back to work.
عندي مريض هنا. سأعود للعمل.
Bye.
الوداع.
Done.
منتهي.
You know what? My boyfriend got back together with his ex.
هل تعلم؟ حبيبي عاد إلى حبيبته السابقة.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I'll find you a better one, okay?
سأجد لك واحدا أفضل، حسنًا؟
No, I just want him!
لا، أريده فقط!
Mr. Wu.
السيد وو.
Let's get back to work first.
دعونا نعود إلى العمل أولاً.
Come on.
تعال.
Mr. Wu.
السيد وو.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I've checked this contract with Legal Affairs.
لقد قمت بمراجعة هذا العقد مع الشؤون القانونية.
Do you have any questions?
هل لديك أي أسئلة؟
No.
لا.
I was thinking about something else just now.
كنت أفكر في شيء آخر الآن.
Isn't Chi Cheng the one checking this contract?
أليس تشي تشنغ هو الذي يقوم بفحص هذا العقد؟
Why did you come to me this time?
لماذا أتيت إلي هذه المرة؟
I don't know where Mr. Chi is these days.
لا أعلم أين السيد تشي هذه الأيام.
I can't reach him.
لا أستطيع الوصول إليه.
Here.
هنا.
These are loquats from my hometown.
هذه هي السفرجل من مسقط رأسي.
Share them with our colleagues.
شاركها مع زملائنا.
Okay.
تمام.
(Chi Cheng)
(تشي تشنغ)
Chi Cheng.
تشي تشنغ.
I've been waiting for so long. I'm going to kill you, jerk!
لقد انتظرت طويلاً. سأقتلك أيها الأحمق!
You were freaking cheated on...
لقد تم خداعك بشكل فظيع...
and you're still being a fool, waiting there.
ومازلت أحمقًا تنتظر هناك.
What did you tell me before?
ماذا قلت لي من قبل؟
You were so ruthless.
لقد كنت قاسياً جداً.
You said when he comes back, you were going to kill him.
قلت عندما يعود، أنك ستقتله.
Now that he's back,
الآن وقد عاد،
you're sucking up to him.
أنت تتملق له.
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
(Chi Cheng)
(تشي تشنغ)
I'm here to see Er Bao.
أنا هنا لرؤية إير باو.
Yes. That's what I'll say.
نعم، هذا ما سأقوله.
Where's Chi Cheng?
أين تشي تشنغ؟
He ended his lease.
لقد انتهى عقد إيجاره.
When?
متى؟
Just a couple of days before.
قبل بضعة أيام فقط.
Why did he end his lease?
لماذا أنهى عقد الإيجار؟
Isn't it obvious? He's from a rich family.
أليس هذا واضحًا؟ إنه من عائلة غنية.
He just wants to stay here for a change...
إنه يريد فقط البقاء هنا للتغيير...
and experience life.
وتجربة الحياة.
After a while, who can stand living here?
بعد فترة من الزمن، من يستطيع أن يتحمل العيش هنا؟
"Experience life"?
"تجربة الحياة"؟
You've experienced it for six years.
لقد مررت بهذه التجربة لمدة ست سنوات.
You could stand it at first, but now you can't.
كان بإمكانك تحمل ذلك في البداية، لكن الآن لا تستطيع.
Poor Er Bao...
المسكين إير باو...
for being with a heartbreaker like you.
لأني مع شخص محطم القلوب مثلك.
I should've stolen the snake back then.
كان ينبغي لي أن أسرق الثعبان في ذلك الوقت.
What? What did you say?
ماذا؟ ماذا قلت؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
It's already the last day.
إنه اليوم الأخير بالفعل.
You're here.
انت هنا.
Looks like it's going to work today.
يبدو أن الأمر سينجح اليوم.
I can use reverse psychology now.
أستطيع أن أستخدم علم النفس العكسي الآن.
Da Wei, how's it going?
دا وي، كيف حالك؟
Pretty good.
جيد جدًا.
Good times are coming. Let's go out for a meal.
أوقات جميلة قادمة. هيا نخرج لتناول وجبة.
We really need to celebrate.
نحن بحاجة حقا للاحتفال.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
In the past few days, Chi Cheng...
في الأيام القليلة الماضية، تشي تشنغ...
really didn't bother you?
هل حقا لم يزعجك؟
No.
لا.
At first, I was worried...
في البداية كنت قلقا...
Chi Cheng would change his mind halfway through.
تشي تشنغ سوف يغير رأيه في منتصف الطريق.
After talking to Guo Cheng Yu, I realized...
بعد التحدث مع Guo Cheng Yu، أدركت...
that we were worrying for nothing.
أننا كنا قلقين من أجل لا شيء.
What did you two talk about?
ماذا تحدثتم عنه؟
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
About the three of them.
عن الثلاثة منهم.
I realized...
لقد أدركت...
that I'm becoming more interested in Wang Shuo.
لقد أصبحت مهتمة أكثر بـ وانغ شو.
Before, I only thought he was handsome and top-notch.
في السابق، كنت أعتقد فقط أنه كان وسيمًا ورائعًا.
Now, I realized...
الآن أدركت...
he's a heartthrob.
إنه محبوب.
And he's very talented.
وهو موهوب جدًا.
He's good at all Chinese and Western instruments.
إنه جيد في جميع الآلات الموسيقية الصينية والغربية.
He held a concert in high school.
أقام حفلة موسيقية في المدرسة الثانوية.
He even wrote a song for Chi Cheng.
حتى أنه كتب أغنية لتشي تشنغ.
And he's very fit.
وهو لائق جداً.
He's a top-ranked national athlete.
إنه أحد الرياضيين المصنفين على المستوى الوطني.
Isn't that exaggerated?
أليس هذا مبالغ فيه؟
No.
لا.
Guo Cheng Yu slept with him once...
لقد نامت Guo Cheng Yu معه مرة واحدة ...
and he's been reminiscing about it for six years.
وقد ظل يتذكرها لمدة ست سنوات.
Let alone Chi Cheng...
دعونا وحدنا تشي تشنغ...
who were with him for three years.
الذين كانوا معه لمدة ثلاث سنوات.
He'll reminisce about it for the rest of his life.
وسوف يتذكر ذلك لبقية حياته.
Who can get rid...
من يستطيع التخلص...
of such a deep cancer.
من هذا السرطان العميق.
Can you?
هل تستطيع؟
You can't.
لا يمكنك.
Look at your small frame.
أنظر إلى إطارك الصغير.
It's obvious that you can't.
من الواضح أنك لا تستطيع ذلك.
I don't even want to get rid of it.
أنا لا أريد حتى التخلص منه.
Yes.
نعم.
And he's very bold.
وهو جريء جدًا.
He dared to sleep with another man...
لقد تجرأ على النوم مع رجل آخر...
behind Chi Cheng's back.
خلف ظهر تشي تشنغ.
Do you dare to do that? I'm sure you don't.
هل تجرؤ على فعل ذلك؟ أنا متأكد أنك لا تفعل.
You don't even dare to sleep with Chi Cheng,
أنت لا تجرؤ حتى على النوم مع تشي تشنغ،
let alone betray him.
ناهيك عن خيانته.
That's because I don't like him.
هذا لأنني لا أحبه.
Yes.
نعم.
You don't like him.
أنت لا تحبه.
I'm just joking with you.
أنا فقط أمزح معك.
Why are you so mad?
لماذا انت غاضبة هكذا؟
Mad?
مجنون؟
Who's mad? How can you say that I'm mad?
من مجنون؟ كيف تقول إني مجنون؟
Look. You're getting angrier.
انظر، أنت تصبح أكثر غضبًا.
Da Wei.
دا وي.
You look pale.
أنت تبدو شاحبًا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Is there something on your mind?
هل هناك شيء في ذهنك؟
I'm too excited.
أنا متحمس جدًا.
Da Bao.
حقيبة جلدية.
Anyone can be mad at me,
يمكن لأي شخص أن يغضب مني،
but not you.
ولكن ليس أنت.
Because when you're angry,
لأنه عندما تغضب،
I'll be anxious.
سوف أكون قلقا.
Even if you don't do anything,
حتى لو لم تفعل شيئا،
I'll still like you.
سأظل أحبك.
I promise.
أعدك.
In the future, I won't let you get hurt again.
في المستقبل، لن أسمح لك بأن تتأذى مرة أخرى.
You're just my little loser.
أنت مجرد خاسرتي الصغيرة.
I'm mesmerized by your loser aura.
أنا مفتون بهالة الخاسر الخاص بك.
Liar.
كذاب.
You're such a liar.
أنت كاذب حقا.
It's already 11pm.
لقد أصبحت الساعة 11 مساءً.
Only one more hour...
ساعة واحدة فقط...
before you reconcile with the man you love but can't have.
قبل أن تتصالحي مع الرجل الذي تحبينه ولكن لا تستطيعين الحصول عليه.
After another hour,
وبعد ساعة أخرى،
we'll have nothing to do with each other, Chi Cheng.
لن يكون لدينا أي علاقة مع بعضنا البعض، تشي تشنغ.
Hang in there.
إصمد.
With this slight breeze,
مع هذا النسيم الخفيف،
tomorrow will be another beautiful day.
غدا سيكون يوما جميلا آخر.
What time is it?
أي ساعة؟
Darn it. Why isn't it midnight yet?
يا إلهي! لماذا لم يحن منتصف الليل بعد؟
He's a heartthrob.
إنه محبوب القلوب.
And he's very talented.
وهو موهوب جدًا.
He's good at all Chinese and Western instruments.
إنه جيد في جميع الآلات الموسيقية الصينية والغربية.
Guo Cheng Yu slept with him once...
لقد نامت Guo Cheng Yu معه مرة واحدة ...
and he's been reminiscing about it for six years.
وقد ظل يتذكرها لمدة ست سنوات.
Let alone Chi Cheng.
دعنا وحدنا تشي تشنغ.
I used to fantasize about being with him forever.
كنت أحلم بالبقاء معه إلى الأبد.
If his original lover is back,
إذا عاد حبيبه الأصلي،
Chi Cheng will lose interest in you.
تشي تشنغ سوف يفقد الاهتمام بك.
I don't care if you can write songs or not.
لا يهمني إذا كنت تستطيع كتابة الأغاني أم لا.
I don't care if you're bold! I don't care if you're fit!
لا يهمني إن كنتَ جريئًا! لا يهمني إن كنتَ لائقًا بدنيًا!
He's mine now.
إنه ملكي الآن.
You're mine now!
أنت لي الآن!
Get lost as far as you can!
إبتعد بقدر ما تستطيع!
I thought you wouldn't show up until 11:59pm.
اعتقدت أنك لن تظهر حتى الساعة 11:59 مساءً.
Looks like I overestimated your willpower.
يبدو أنني بالغت في تقدير قوة إرادتك.
You're mine.
أنت لي.
I'm yours.
أنا لك.
Then you can't sleep with him from now on.
إذن لن تتمكني من النوم معه من الآن فصاعدا.
I won't sleep with him.
لن أنام معه.
Only with you.
معك فقط.
Then from now on,
ومن الآن فصاعدا،
when you're with me,
عندما تكون معي
don't think about him.
لا تفكر فيه
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Why would I think about him?
لماذا أفكر فيه؟
I'm warning you.
انا احذرك.
That's all his own business.
هذا كله شأنه الخاص.
No matter how talented he is, it's his business.
مهما كانت موهبته، فهذا شأنه.
From now on, you'll only hear my clear singing voice.
من الآن فصاعدا، لن تسمع إلا صوتي الغنائي الواضح.
No matter how fit he is, it's still his business.
بغض النظر عن مدى لياقته البدنية، فهذا لا يزال عمله.
You shouldn't be concerned about his body.
لا ينبغي أن تقلق بشأن جسده.
You should be concerned about the wound on my neck and chest.
يجب أن تشعر بالقلق بشأن الجرح الموجود على رقبتي وصدري.
I don't care if he's bold.
لا يهمني إذا كان جريئا.
Don't use his integrity as a standard...
لا تستخدم نزاهته كمعيار...
and treat my self-respect...
وعامل احترامي لذاتي...
as nothing.
كأنه لا شيء.
Jiang Xiao Shuai is really good at making things up.
جيانج شياو شواي جيد حقًا في اختلاق الأشياء.
All right.
حسنًا.
I told you. I'm yours.
لقد قلت لك. أنا لك.
Are you mine then?
هل أنت لي إذن؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Fine.
بخير.
Since you're mine,
بما أنك لي،
shouldn't we get a certificate?
ألا ينبغي لنا أن نحصل على شهادة؟
In this society, it's really hard if you don't have a certificate.
في هذا المجتمع، من الصعب حقًا ألا يكون لديك شهادة.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
If you don't have a certificate with me,
إذا لم يكن لديك شهادة معي،
who will you complain to if I run away one day?
من ستشتكي إليه إذا هربت يومًا ما؟
If you run away,
إذا هربت،
I'll find someone else to get a certificate with.
سأبحث عن شخص آخر للحصول على الشهادة معه.
Who the heck dares to steal my man?
من الذي يجرؤ على سرقة رجلي؟
What?
ماذا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm at a friend's house.
أنا في منزل صديق.
That Snake Lord's flight lands at midnight in three days.
ستصل رحلة سيد الثعابين في منتصف الليل بعد ثلاثة أيام.
I'm busy.
انا مشغول.
If you're not free to come home now,
إذا لم تكن حرًا في العودة إلى المنزل الآن،
I'll make time tomorrow...
سأجد الوقت غدًا...
to tear down your stupid art installation company.
لهدم شركة تركيب الفن الغبية الخاصة بك.
- Come on. - Wait for me.
- هيا. - انتظرني.
Let's continue with the certificate.
دعونا نستمر مع الشهادة.
I have to go home.
يجب علي أن أعود إلى المنزل.
My dad called me.
لقد اتصل بي والدي.
Was it really your dad?
هل كان حقا والدك؟
It really was.
لقد كان كذلك بالفعل.
Since your dad is calling you at this hour,
بما أن والدك يتصل بك في هذه الساعة،
it must be urgent.
يجب أن يكون الأمر عاجلا.
Go.
يذهب.
Do you think it's easy for me to wait for this day?
هل تعتقد أنه من السهل بالنسبة لي أن أنتظر هذا اليوم؟
Wait for me to come back.
انتظرني حتى أعود.
Young Master Guo.
السيد الشاب قوه.
Do you think Chi Cheng succeeded?
هل تعتقد أن تشي تشنغ نجح؟
He scared Jiang Xiao Shuai so much.
لقد أخاف جيانغ شياو شواي كثيرًا.
How can I easily let him succeed?
كيف يمكنني أن أسمح له بالنجاح بسهولة؟
Ask to meet Wu Suo Wei.
اطلب مقابلة وو سو وي.
Tell him...
أخبره...
it's to discuss a collaboration.
لمناقشة التعاون.
Where?
أين؟
Shengshi Club.
نادي شينجشي.
That's intense.
هذا مكثف.
(Shengshi Club)
(نادي شينغشي)
- Don't be shy. - Young Master Guo.
- لا تكن خجولاً. - السيد الشاب قوه.
Xiao Tian.
شياو تيان.
Behave yourself.
أحسن التصرف.
I'm here to talk business.
أنا هنا للتحدث عن العمل.
Do you come here often?
هل تأتي إلى هنا في كثير من الأحيان؟
Not as often as Chi Cheng.
ليس بقدر تشي تشنغ.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
By the way, Young Master Chi hasn't been here for a long time.
بالمناسبة، السيد الشاب تشي لم يكن هنا منذ وقت طويل.
What has he been up to lately? I miss him so much.
ماذا كان يفعل مؤخرًا؟ أفتقده كثيرًا.
We're here.
نحن هنا.
Come on.
تعال.
Accompany him well today, guys.
رافقوه جيدًا اليوم يا شباب.
- Okay. - Sure!
-حسنا. -بالتأكيد!
I need to take this call.
أحتاج إلى الرد على هذه المكالمة.
Have fun.
استمتع.
You're straight, right?
أنت مستقيم، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Does Chi Cheng come here often?
هل يأتي تشي تشنغ إلى هنا في كثير من الأحيان؟
For a period of time, he came here every day.
لمدة من الزمن، كان يأتي إلى هنا كل يوم.
He even stayed the night.
حتى أنه بقي طوال الليل.
What does he do here?
ماذا يفعل هنا؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Could he really...
هل يمكنه حقا...
come here to sing and dance?
هل اتيتم الى هنا للغناء والرقص؟
Mr. Chi likes hardcore things.
السيد تشي يحب الأشياء الصعبة.
When you entered, did you notice the second room by the door?
عندما دخلت هل لاحظت الغرفة الثانية بجانب الباب؟
As soon as Mr. Chi enters it,
بمجرد دخول السيد تشي إليها،
the room is filled with cries and moans.
كانت الغرفة مليئة بالصراخ والأنين.
He's so into it.
إنه مهتم بذلك كثيراً.
Did he pick you many times?
هل اختارك عدة مرات؟
I'm the one he picks the most.
أنا الشخص الذي يختاره أكثر.
He says I'm obedient.
يقول أنني مطيع.
He can torture me...
هو يستطيع تعذيبي...
however he wants.
مهما كان ما يريد.
Look.
ينظر.
Look at this cigarette burn.
أنظر إلى حرق السجائر هذا.
Young Master Chi did it.
لقد فعلها السيد الشاب تشي.
Why are you leaving?
لماذا تغادر؟
Something came up at work. I have to go.
حدث شيء ما في العمل. يجب أن أذهب.
Come on. Let's have fun!
هيا، لنستمتع!
Let's have fun!
دعونا نستمتع!
He hasn't shown up all day.
لم يظهر طيلة اليوم.
He didn't contact me either.
ولم يتصل بي أيضًا.
He must have completed the mission.
لابد أنه أكمل المهمة.
Please bless me.
من فضلك باركني.
Please let it be successful.
أرجو أن يكون ناجحا.
Please.
لو سمحت.
I'm so mad.
أنا غاضبة جداً.
What's wrong? What happened?
ما الخطب؟ ماذا حدث؟
I accidentally entered Chi Cheng's den of lust.
دخلت عن طريق الخطأ إلى وكر الشهوة الخاص بـ تشي تشنغ.
The male escort told me all about his dirty secrets.
أخبرني المرافق الذكر بكل أسراره القذرة.
Now, I want to destroy him.
الآن أريد تدميره.
Isn't it too late for you to find out now?
أليس من المتأخر جدًا أن تكتشف ذلك الآن؟
Didn't you already sleep with Chi Cheng yesterday?
ألم تنم مع تشي تشنغ بالأمس؟
Almost.
بالكاد.
If his dad didn't call him home urgently,
إذا لم يتصل به والده إلى المنزل على وجه السرعة،
I'd regret that to death.
سأندم على ذلك حتى الموت.
Why would I sleep with him?
لماذا أريد أن أنام معه؟
He's lucky if I don't break up with him.
إنه محظوظ إذا لم أنفصل عنه.
It's over.
انتهى.
All my efforts are in vain.
كل جهودي ذهبت سدى.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Is there anyone else at your home?
هل هناك أي شخص آخر في منزلك؟
No. Why?
لا. لماذا؟
Can I hide here for a couple of days?
هل يمكنني الاختباء هنا لبضعة أيام؟
Please.
لو سمحت.
You can hide here forever.
يمكنك الاختباء هنا إلى الأبد.
If you say that, I'll get going then.
إذا قلت ذلك، سأذهب حينها.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Then...
ثم...
what about the clinic?
ماذا عن العيادة؟
This is good for me. I can rest for a couple of days.
هذا جيد بالنسبة لي. أستطيع أن أرتاح لبضعة أيام.
Rest?
استراحة؟
This place...
هذا المكان...
is most suitable for resting.
هو الأكثر ملاءمة للراحة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'll be gentle.
سوف أكون لطيفا.
He has a private doctor at home.
لديه طبيب خاص في المنزل.
Why does he keep coming to my clinic then?
لماذا يستمر في المجيء إلى عيادتي إذن؟
Take a look. What do you want to eat?
ألقِ نظرة. ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
I'll make it for you.
سأفعل ذلك لك.
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
I haven't been able to reach you since last night.
لم أتمكن من الوصول إليك منذ الليلة الماضية.
Can't you hear me?
هل لا تسمعني؟
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
What does this mean?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
I think you're dirty.
أعتقد أنك قذر.
- What? - I said,
- ماذا؟ - قلت،
I think...
أظن...
you're dirty.
أنت قذر.
You think I'm dirty?
هل تعتقد أنني قذرة؟
Yes, Shengshi Club's No. 6 male escort, Xiao Tian,
نعم، المرافق رقم 6 لنادي شينغشي ، شياو تيان،
asked me to tell you...
طلب مني أن أخبرك...
that he misses you.
أنه يفتقدك.
Did you have to go there to investigate me?
هل كان عليك الذهاب إلى هناك للتحقيق معي؟
I don't know how many people I've slept with.
لا أعرف عدد الأشخاص الذين نمت معهم.
I used to be this dirty.
لقد كنت قذرة هكذا.
It's not too late for you to regret it now.
لم يفت الأوان بعد لتندم على ذلك الآن.
If I regret it, would I have scolded you?
لو ندمت هل كنت سأوبخك؟
What's wrong with scolding you a bit?
ما الخطأ في توبيخك قليلاً؟
For the little dirty things you did, shouldn't I scold you?
بالنسبة للأشياء الصغيرة القذرة التي فعلتها، ألا يجب أن أوبخك؟
I'm unhappy. I just want to say it out loud.
أنا حزين. أريد فقط أن أقول ذلك بصوت عالٍ.
I think you're dirty.
أعتقد أنك قذر.
Are you and Wu Suo Wei...
هل أنت و وو سو وي...
still together?
هل مازلتم معًا؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Do you want us to break up?
هل تريد منا أن ننفصل؟
No. I just see that you're not in a good mood.
لا، أرى فقط أنك لست في مزاج جيد.
He won't let me touch him.
لن يسمح لي بلمسه.
Why?
لماذا؟
He...
هو...
thinks I'm dirty.
يعتقد أنني قذر.
How dare he think...
كيف يجرؤ على التفكير...
that you're...
أنك...
Why?
لماذا؟
He dug up my dirty secrets.
لقد كشف أسرارى القذرة.
Isn't this karma?
أليس هذا هو الكارما؟
What?
ماذا؟
Say that again.
قل ذلك مرة أخرى.
I didn't say anything.
لم اقل شيئا.
Pull over at the pharmacy.
توقف عند الصيدلية.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Get me some medicine.
احضر لي بعض الدواء.
What medicine?
أي دواء؟
Something that can freaking decrease my libido.
شيء يمكن أن يقلل بشكل كبير من رغبتي الجنسية.
This won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
I have to think of something.
يجب علي أن أفكر في شيء ما.
Size 80.
المقاس 80.
Size 82.1.
المقاس 82.1.
This is...
هذا هو...
Xiao Tian.
شياو تيان.
Chi Cheng and I have arrived Shengshi Club.
لقد وصلنا أنا وتشي تشنغ إلى نادي شينغشي.
- When are you coming? - Shengshi Club?
- متى ستأتي؟ - نادي شنغشي؟
I'm sorry. I sent it by mistake.
انا آسف لقد أرسلته بالخطأ.
He sent it by mistake?
أرسله بالخطأ؟
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
He went there again.
لقد ذهب هناك مرة أخرى.
I knew he wouldn't be able to endure it.
كنت أعلم أنه لن يكون قادرًا على تحمل ذلك.
That perverted mutt!
هذا الكلب المنحرف!
I'm going to kill him!
سأقتله!
Mr. Chi.
السيد تشي.
Didn't you say a client wants to see me...
ألم تقل أن العميل يريد رؤيتي؟
to order some art installations?
لطلب بعض التركيبات الفنية؟
Why did you bring me here?
لماذا احضرتني هنا؟
The client will be here soon.
العميل سيكون هنا قريبا.
Let's have some fun first.
دعونا نستمتع ببعض المرح أولاً.
Young Master Chi, you're finally here.
السيد الشاب تشي، أنت هنا أخيرًا.
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
Young Master Chi, he kicked me.
السيد الشاب تشي، لقد ركلني.
Young Master Chi.
السيد الشاب تشي.
I'll spank him when we get home.
سأضربه عندما نصل إلى المنزل.
Listen up, everyone!
استمعوا جميعا!
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
we will bid this place farewell forever.
سوف نقول وداعا لهذا المكان إلى الأبد.
I'm sorry for not supporting your business anymore.
أنا آسف لعدم دعم عملك بعد الآن.
Who wants to see him?
من يريد رؤيته؟
Take a good look.
خذ نظرة جيدة.
Once he's out of this door,
بمجرد خروجه من هذا الباب،
you won't get the chance to look at him again.
لن تحصل على فرصة للنظر إليه مرة أخرى.
What does this mean?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
Let's go home and get a certificate.
دعونا نذهب إلى المنزل ونحصل على الشهادة.
It's really worrying when you go out without a certificate nowadays.
إنه أمر مقلق حقًا عندما تخرج بدون شهادة في هذه الأيام.
Where are we?
أين نحن؟
My new home.
بيتي الجديد.
However...
لكن...
It's going to be your new home soon too,
وسوف يكون منزلك الجديد قريبًا أيضًا،
my little master.
سيدي الصغير.